onewayfurniture.com 2013-03-25

# Your Privacy is Our Priority

**Your privacy is very important to us.**

We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties. Please read this privacy policy to learn more about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information. We want you to fully understand our privacy practices and therefore we have created this section to help you fully evaluate our practices and answer privacy questions.

 ** _OneWayFurniture.com Privacy Policy_**

This site www.onewayfurniture.com (“One Way Furniture”) is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the [Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/details.html) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information. Your privacy is very important to us. We want to make your experience on the Internet as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and we want you to use our gallery’s array of information, tools, and opportunities with complete confidence. We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how One Way Furniture collects information from all users of [ One Way Furniture ](http://www./) both those who contact us without making a purchase ("Visitors") as well as those who make a purchase ("Customers"); what we do with the information we collect, and the choices Visitors and Customers have concerning the collection and use of such information. One Way Furniture requests that you read this Privacy Policy carefully. 

**_Introduction_**

One Way Furniture is structured around a Yahoo! Store. Any information provided on our Web site is collected by Yahoo! Store on their servers from Visitors and Customers who access the web site. That information is then shared with One Way Furniture. This information includes ordering information such as shipping and billing names and addresses, phone numbers, email addresses and credit card information. (See “Orders” below.) We use this information primarily to fulfill customer orders and requests. We do not share this information with any third parties except as described in this privacy policy. However, we may disclose personal information collected if we have received your permission beforehand or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that such disclosure is required by law or other special cases described below.

 ** _Orders and Use of Personally Identifiable Information (PII)_**

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain PII from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

If your PII changes, or if you no longer desire remain as a One Way Furniture customer, you may correct, update, or delete it by emailing Customer Support at 1-800-789-1995.

  * **Registration**
\- Once you place an order you may be asked if you would like to create a username and password for your account if you use our customer support help desk. We use this information to contact you about the services on our site and so that you can track your order information.
  *  **Testimonials**
\- If we receive permission to post testimonials from your shopping experience, we only post first names and last initials. Your PII information is fully protected.
 ** _Security_**

If you feel uncomfortable shopping online please call us toll free at 1-800-789-1995. You may also e-mail, or fax your order. Please do not e-mail us your credit card information, only do that via telephone, fax or online at our Yahoo! Store page. The ordering information you provide - including credit card information - is secured using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology via Yahoo! Store servers. Yahoo! Store uses SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption when transmitting certain kinds of information, such as financial services information or payment information. An icon resembling a padlock is displayed on the bottom of most browsers window during SSL transactions that involve credit cards and other forms of payment. Any time a Yahoo! Store asks for a credit card number during checkout for payment, it will be SSL encrypted. The information you provide will be stored securely on Yahoo! servers. This SSL technology is used to prevent such information from being intercepted and read as it is transmitted over the Internet. The encrypted data goes to a secure site where your information is stored on restricted-access computers located at restricted-access sites. While Yahoo! makes every effort to ensure the integrity and security of its network and systems, they cannot guarantee that their security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience using cookies (See “Use of Cookies” below). Please see the Yahoo! Privacy Policy for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information. 

**_Use Of Cookies_**

We use cookies on this site. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies for anonymous statistical tracking of the pages you visit which enables us to identify the popularity of any given page. Only your computer’s IP address is tracked, but not any of your PII. A session ID cookie expires 30 days after you leave the site.

A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. We set a persistent cookie to allow you to revisit One Way Furniture’s checkout system at a later date without having to reenter your personal information (excluding financial information.) This cookie is tied to PII only for this purpose. This cookie is not used for tracking purposes of any kind.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site without affecting your ability to surf through or purchase on our web site. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by One Way Furniture only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. Some of our business partners (e.g., Yahoo Analytics) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies.

 ** _Links To Other Sites_**

This Web site may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by One Way Furniture. Please be aware that we, One Way Furniture, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by One Way Furniture. 

**_Communications from the Site_**

  *  **Special Offer and Updates**
\- We will occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals, and promotions. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out.”
  *  **Newsletters**
\- If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section.
  *  **Email a Friend**
\- If you choose to use our referral service to email a friend about our site/products, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. One Way Furniture does not store this information and uses it for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.
  *  **Service Related Announcements**
\- We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. We will send you an order confirmation email. We will also respond to any inquiry you send to us via email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.
**_Choice/Opt Out_**

We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference during our order process or in our confirmation email. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication. Or you may phone us at 1-800-789-1995 or Contact Us You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.

 ** _Log Files_**

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click stream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. We use a third-party tracking service that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate to capture usage and volume statistics to improve our site.

 ** _Information Sharing and Disclosure_**

  * **Aggregate Information (Non Personally Identifiable)**
\- We share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our marketing partners and advertisers. This information does not identify individual users. We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information.
  *  **Personally Identifiable Information**
\- We DO NOT Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties except as described in this privacy policy.
  *  **Service Providers**
\- We use other third parties to provide credit card processing, shipping services and email fulfillment services. When you purchase a product from our site or when we send emails to you, we will share your contact information including email address, credit card information, and/or shipping information as necessary for the third party to provide a particular service. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose including their own marketing purposes.
**_Legal Disclaimer_**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

 ** _Public Forums / Blogs_**

One Way Furniture does not collect any personal information on our blog and only posts content. Our Blog does not accept any comments from Visitors.

 _ **Access to Personally Identifiable Information**_

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, or delete your personally identifiable information by opening a Customer Support help ticket on our site. You can also call us at 1-800-789-1995 . You can update or change your account information by contacting our Customer Support or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

 ** _Changes To This Privacy Statement_**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

 _ **Truste Privacy Seal License**_

Onewayfurniture.com is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the site www.onewayfurniture.com. Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact customer service by email support (at) onewayfurniture.com or call us toll free at 1-800-789-1995. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe <http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php>. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns. Privacy Statement Created: 1/25/2009

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a prominent notice on our home page.

One Way Furniture  
535 Broadhollow Rd - Ste A7 (Not for returns)   
Melville, N.Y 11747  
1-800-789-1995
